Hives of horror!
The Deadly Bees is a horror, thriller film directed by Freddie Francis.
Pop singer Vicki Robbins collapses from exhaustion while shooting ta music video; her
physician prescribes a respite on Seagull Island with beekeeper Ralph Hargrove.
Initially finding the Hargroves' bitter marital strife oddly relaxing, the arrival
of specially-bred attack bees pushes Vicki to her survival instinct.
Vicki Robbins, played by Suzanna Leigh.
H.W. Manfred, played by Frank Finlay.
Ralph Hargrove, played by Guy Doleman.
Mary Hargrove, played by Catherine Finn.
Thompson, played by John Harvey.
David Hawkins, played by Michael Ripper.
The Deadly Bees  is a 1967 British horror film based on H.
Heard's 1941 novel A Taste for Honey.
It was directed by Freddie Francis, and stars Suzanna
Leigh, Guy Doleman, and Frank Finlay.
The original screenplay was by Robert Bloch but
was rewritten by Anthony Marriott.
The film was released theatrically in the United States in 1967 and was
featured in a 1998 episode of Mystery Science Theater 3000.
Heard's novel, which was a sort of Sherlock Holmes pastiche, had been previously adapted for television as a 60-minute drama episode of The Elgin Hour: season
1, episode 11 under the title "Sting of Death" (22 February 1955), starring Boris Karloff as the detective character from Heard's novel, Mr.
According to H.
Heard's official website, kinescopes of this TV dramatisation survive, and, in 2014, it was made commercially available for home video as
one of several features in a DVD, released by Synergy Entertainment, titled Sherlock Holmes: The Archive Collection Vol.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, beehive, singer, dog, bee.
The tone is dark and intense.